[intro to "Let Me Entertain
You" by Robbie Williams]
[Robbie Williams VO] Good
evening, folks, hmm...
Good evening, you slags.
No, good evening, folks.
So, who is Robbie Williams?
Well, I've been
called many things -
narcissistic, punchable,
shit-eating twat,
but while I'm all those things,
I wanna show you how
I really see myself.
So sit back, relax,
while I give you a right
fucking entertaining.
So, the story starts...
[Robbie VO] 1982,
Stoke-on-Trent.
The arse-end of the
north of England.
[boy 1] Mitchell.
It may look grubby
and deprived...
- [boy 2] Troy.
- But deep down...
- [boy 1] Wayne.
- ...it was grubby and deprived.
[boy 2] Mason.
I didn't have much,
but at least I
had the respect...
- [boy 1] Crystal.
- ...and admiration of my peers.
[Robbie] What?!
[Robbie VO] They just
had trouble showing it.
- [boy 2] Robert.
- Yes! Come on! [grunts]
Oi! Right, knobhead,
pass the ball to Nate
and let him do the rest.
Positions!
Oi! The fuck you off
to? You're in goal.
- But...
- Don't fuck it up.
I'm like a chainmail condom,
nothing's getting through.
Whoo! Let's go, slags!
[Robbie VO] I had
plenty of balls.
But I couldn't
stop a single one.
I wasn't ready. Ohh!
- [boy] Nice one, dickhead.
- Come on!
[Robbie screaming] Oh!
Robert Williams,
captain of Port Vale.
[children roaring]
[thudding] [children laughing]
[boy] You really are
fucking useless, aren't ya?
[children laughing]
[girl] Little bitch!
It's alright, Rob.
Nate, just leave it.
Yeah... Yeah, jog on, you tit.
- [children laughing]
- Right, come on, let's go.
You're a fucking nobody!
[sniffles]
[Robbie VO] See,
where I grew up,
you were meant to act small.
But the thing is,
my DNA is cabaret.
I came out of the
womb with jazz hands.
Which was very
painful for my mum.
[Janet] Heading
downstairs for a bit.
One of the barmen's
called in sick.
Goodnight, sweetheart.
Straight to bed, yeah? [kisses]
- Don't let him ruin his dinner.
- Bye, love.
[Frank Sinatra singing]
♪ And now the end is near
[Robbie singing] ♪ And so
I face the final curtain ♪
[Robbie and Peter] ♪ My friend
[Peter] ♪ I'll make it clear
How's about a warm hand
on my entrance? [laughs]
[Sinatra] ♪ Of
which I'm certain
[Peter] ♪ Of which I'm certain
[both singing] ♪ I've
lived a life that's full ♪
♪ I've travelled each
and every highway ♪
- ♪ And more... ♪
- [Peter] Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you...
♪ I did it my way
[Robbie VO] My dad
was well enamoured
by the stars of the day -
Dean Martin, Sammy Davis
Jr and, of course, Sinatra.
They were gods to him.
Youth, you hear that?
That's pure love, that is.
It don't come cheap, mind.
You've got to risk it
all - whatever it takes.
Because if you make it...
...it's paradise.
Thing is, you can't learn it.
You're either born with it...
...or you're a nobody.
♪ And more
♪ Much more than
this, I did it... ♪
- Light 'em up!
[both singing] ♪
Yes, there were times
♪ I guess you knew
♪ When I bit off more
than I could chew ♪
[Robbie giggles]
♪ And through it all
when there was doubt ♪
♪ I ate it up and spit it out
♪ I grew tall and
through it all ♪
- Dad! Dad!
- ♪ And did it my...
- [music stops]
- Oh, fuck it!
- Now, look what you've...
- Sorry.
I had a full head of
steam then, and all.
- I can fix it.
- Get out the way.
- We can sing without it.
- It's not the same.
- Or... or we could...
- Robert!
I think it's time for a bath.
But I want to keep going.
Just go with your nan, will ya!
[Betty] Come on, love. Come on.
[Peter] Stupid...
Come on, blue eyes...
- ♪ My way... ♪
- Yes.
[water runs]
- Nan?
- Hm-mm.
[water stops]
What is...'it'?
[Betty] What do you mean?
Dad said you have to
be born with 'it'...
- ...and maybe I wasn't.
- Ohhh.
Believe me, whatever 'it' is,
you got more than your share.
You're just saying that.
I'm bloody well not.
I wouldn't change a
hair on your head.
What is it, love?
I don't want to be a nobody.
Oh, love, there's no
such thing as a nobody.
Remember...
This might feel good.
But this...
...this is what matters.
You're enough.
[piano playing]
[Robbie VO] I was
nine years old
when I got my first real
taste of the limelight.
And I still remember
that taste -
pure, unadulterated terror.
[Candice] Have you seen the
fit one with the big bulge?
After the show, I'm
going to touch him
where his bathing suit goes.
I'm going to fuck
it up, I know it.
So what? No one will notice.
My dad will.
Just go out there, sing your
fucking song and walk off.
That's not enough! He'll
see right through me.
What am I going to do?
I don't know. I'm just
doing this for the sausage.
[children finish singing]
[audience applauding]
[Robbie VO] In the
next three seconds,
I'm going to be found out.
They'll see that I'm ugly,
I'm stupid, I'm untalented.
I'm not good at anything.
[children screaming]
[thudding]
[audience gasping]
[smattering of laughter]
[Robbie VO] But there is
one skill I'd practised
more than any other
child in the world.
Light 'em up.
[Robbie VO] And that's
for showing off.
How's about a warm
hand on my entrance?
[laughing and applauding]
[Robbie VO] You see, I
thought to become famous
you had to be
really, really good.
Turns out you just have to
show off and be a bit cheeky.
[woman] Put your hands together
for our next contestant -
- Peter Williams.
- He's probably embarrassed.
[scattered applause]
Thank you very much.
[audience exclaims]
You know the difference between
an 'oooh' and an 'aaaah'?
Well, it's about three inches.
[laughter]
♪ For I am a Pirate King
[chorus] ♪ You are! Hurrah
for the Pirate King ♪
I usually go over
people's heads.
♪ It's great to
be a Pirate King ♪
[chorus] ♪ It is! Hurrah
for the Pirate King ♪
Ooh, naughty!
[chorus] Hurrah
for the Pirate... ♪
♪ Pirate...
[Robbie] Oh, ho,
oh! Eyes off my bum.
[laughter]
♪ ..King
[piano flourish concludes]
[audience applauding]
[all] Hurrah!
[applauding and cheering]
[audience member] Yes, Robert!
Whoo!
[distorted sounds]
[Robbie's inner
voice] You're useless!
You're a disgrace!
[angry footsteps]
[Robbie's inner voice]
You're a fucking nobody!
Look at you...
I fucking hate you.
[Robbie VO] My dad won
five quid that night.
Oh, you're kidding me!
[Robbie VO] Although it might
as well have been five million.
[Peter] Thank you very much.
You have been wonderful
and I've been Peter Will...
Conway. I'm Peter Conway!
[applause]
[Robbie VO] Not only
did he change his name.
He changed his life.
One day he went to
watch the FA Cup Final.
Unfortunately, he
didn't come back.
[all sing]
The audience beckoned
and he left us to be one
step closer to his gods.
["Feel" by Robbie
Williams intro]
♪ Come on hold my hand
♪ I wanna contact the living ♪
♪ Not sure I understand
♪ This role I've been given
♪ I sit and talk to God
♪ He just laughs at my plans
♪ My head speaks a language
♪ I don't understand
♪ I just wanna feel real love ♪
♪ Feel the love ever after
♪ There's a hole in my soul
♪ You can see it in my face
It's a real big place ♪
♪ I need to feel real love
♪ And the love ever after
[comb teeth click]
♪ I cannot get enough
[car horn tooting]
[brakes screech]
Don't worry, Mum.
We'll be alright.
Light 'em up.
♪ I just wanna feel real love
♪ Feel the home that I live in
[Robbie and Peter singing]
♪ 'Cause I got too much life
♪ Running through my
veins going to waste ♪
♪ I just wanna feel real love
♪ Feel the life ever after
♪ There's a hole in my soul
♪ You can see it in my face
It's a real big place ♪
[Robbie singing solo] ♪
Come on hold my... hand
♪ I wanna contact the living ♪
♪ Not sure I understand
♪ This role I've been given
[grand orchestral
vocal flourish]
[bell ringing]
[man] Next!
[man] Take a pamphlet,
sign the form,
shut the door on your way out.
[Robbie] No, you're alright.
I know what I'm going to be.
[man] Oh, aye, what's that then?
Famous! I'm going
to sing and dance.
I'm writing lyrics and all.
I've seen your grades, lad.
You couldn't rub
two words together.
"The world is mine to claim.
"All I need is a
fuckload of fame.
"Ooh, ooh, yeah."
Listen, don't embarrass
yourself, yeah?
This, it's not for you. Keep
your feet on the ground.
[grabs pen]
[puts pen down]
You might want to frame that.
- Tosser!
- [man] Next!
["The Power" by Snap! playing]
♪ I've got the power
Whoo!
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Hey! Oh!
♪ I've got the power
[Robbie moaning]
Oh, do it, Nate!
[Nate] Fuck me! You'd make
a fucking awful stripper.
- You know that?
- [Robbie] Fuck off.
Oh, that's my backup plan.
[Nate] Hey, you should
come work with me.
Flint's always
looking for people.
[Robbie] Isn't he that
flashy cunt in the coupe?
Yeah, but he's proper.
Double glazing.
Easy job, easy money.
How'd you meet him?
- I shagged his mum.
- Fucking hell!
Ah, it's alright, he knows.
His dad wouldn't be
best pleased, though.
[Robbie laughs]
[Nate] Fucking have that!
[beer bottle crashing]
So have you told him
about the trials?
- Nah.
- Well, you better.
That scout was fucking excited.
I thought he was going to blow
you right there on the pitch.
[Nate] Fuck off! I'm
not going to the trials.
- I'm not going to the trials.
- Rubbish.
- I'm not.
- What?
Think of the money.
The supermodels.
The fans screaming for ya.
Yeah, I don't need
all that fancy shit.
- Fucking hell, Nate!
- Alright, calm down.
You've got a ticket to heaven
and you're going to stay here?
Oh, yeah, it's like you
with your singing, isn't it?
I just do it 'cause I love it.
Who gives a fuck if you love it?
What matters is that other
people love you doing it.
[Janet] You'll have to
get yourself to school.
I can't face it.
I've got a bastard
of a headache.
And an exam, which you
better have studied for.
Why do you think
my head's pounding?
You'll have more than a
pounding head if you haven't.
Oh, I love it when
she talks dirty.
- [giggling]
- [Janet] You're going.
I'd take you, but I've
got a million deliveries.
God knows I've already had
one man lounging about...
[radio announcer] A music
manager in Manchester
is holding auditions...
Shh. ...for young men...
Don't you bloody shush me.
- ...in singing and dancing.
- [Robbie] Mum! Shush.
The man behind the venture,
Nigel Martin Smith,
- is creating a new boy band.
- [radio static]
I didn't think you're
interested in boy bands.
Mum, quick. [clings fingers]
Quick! Quick! Write it down.
- Doors open at 9 AM...
- This is it!
- [Betty laughing]
I'm going to be fucking famous!
[man] Shut up, you tit!
Oh, fuck off, Glen!
["La Bamba" by Ritchie
Valens playing]
♪ Para bailar La Bamba ♪
♪ Para bailar La Bamba
♪ Se necesita una
poca de gracia... ♪
Whoo! Whoo!
He makes my tizzer
go foo, he does.
♪ Y arriba y arriba
♪ Ba, Ba, Bamba
Ba, Ba, Bamba ♪
- [music stops]
- [performer pants]
Thank you.
[chatter]
Light 'em up.
[door closes]
I'm Robert.
[Robbie VO] Nigel Martin
Smith was, for legal reasons,
an absolute sweetheart.
Well, go on then.
[Robbie VO] And a
first-class cunt.
[deep breath]
[Robbie singing "Straighten
Up and Fly Right"]
♪ A buzzard took a monkey
for a ride in the air ♪
♪ The monkey thought that
everything was on the square ♪
♪ The buzzard tried to throw
the monkey off of his back ♪
♪ The monkey
grabbed his neck ♪
♪ And said, "Now
listen, Jack" ♪
♪ Straighten up and fly right
♪ Straighten up
and stay right ♪
♪ Straighten up and fly right
♪ Cool down, Papa, don't
you blow your top ♪
♪ Ain't no use in divin'...
[Robbie's inner voice]
He's bored of you.
Look at you. You've
got no talent.
You're not fucking Sinatra.
♪ Straighten up and fly right
♪ Cool down, Papa, don't
you blow your top ♪
Okay, that'll do, lad.
You do know this is a pop band?
Yeah.
Tell you what, I'll
do Milli Vanilli's...
No!
Cheers then.
So, shall we tell them
that you found your man
and they can all fuck
off home then, yeah?
No, don't you get up.
It'll be my pleasure.
[Robbie VO] And if I hadn't
winked in that moment,
none of this would've happened.
I wouldn't even be
here talking to you.
Shhhh!
[Robbie] Break a leg, you slags.
Cheeky little bastard.
[Robbie] He wouldn't know
talent if it jumped up
and bit him on the cock.
It's only been a
few hours, love.
He's got no eye for it, Nan.
You have to wait.
I fucked it.
[kicks wall]
He saw right through me.
I mean, look at me.
Do I look like a
pop star to you?
[Betty] You look
like you always look.
Exactly.
A talentless fuck...
[drops phone]
...who's going to
die alone and fat
and be craned out of
his shitpit in Stoke.
[sighing]
[phone ringing]
[Robbie yelling] Aaagh!
Fuck, Nan! Hello?
[Peter] Youth?
Dad.
[Peter] Um, your
voice is so low now.
Thought I had the wrong number.
- How are you, Dad?
- Never better. Never better.
Now listen, um, I haven't got
long, but, uh, I was thinking -
how about you come visit?
- Really?
- Yeah, why not?
School holidays are coming up.
You should come see what
the old man's been up to.
[quietly] Yes.
I mean, yeah, definitely!
[Peter] Smashing!
Alright, I better go.
A full house waits for
no man and all that!
- It'll be good to see ya, lad.
- Light 'em up, Dad...
[phone disconnects]
[puts receiver down]
- [Betty] Oh, Robert. [laughing]
- Oh! [laughing]
Come on!
[both laughing]
[kisses]
- Oh, love.
- Bloody hell, Nan.
Oh, Lord.
[Peter] Is everybody
having a good time?
[crowd cheering]
Peter can't hear you.
You having a good time?
[crowd roaring and applauding]
[Peter] I was lucky
enough to grace the stage
with this next act at
a talent competition.
I'll never forget it.
He gave me a five.
[crowd] Oooh.
Oh, it was sadder than that.
- Oooh.
- [crowd] Oooh.
So please put your
hands together
for the irresistible...
[piano plays suspenseful music]
...the irrepressible...
...the irreplaceable...
- Ooh!
- [piano plays suspenseful music]
I give him a ten out of
ten - Mr. Terry Swinton.
[crowd applauding]
[Peter] I've warmed
them up for ya.
[intro to "Mack the Knife"]
♪ Oh, the shark has
pretty teeth, dear ♪
I thought I was losing that
stage left table for a bit,
but I won them back, didn't I?
Oh, yeah.
I'm glad you reached out.
It was a shock, but,
you know, in a good way.
I thought it was
about time, youth.
Hey, I forgot to tell you,
I'm joining this pop band.
Really? When...
when do you start?
Well, I'm not definitely
in yet, but...
- Oh...
- Well, no.
It's just that I
haven't heard back...
- [Peter] Watch it!
- [Robbie] Oh, sorry.
♪ Now, Mack, he's spending...
Terry's the bollocks, isn't he?
Yeah.
Actually, you might want to
keep that bed out for me.
Failed my exams -
complete fucking balls-up.
Mum's going to put me on the
first bus back when I tell her.
Fucking hopeless.
You've got to learn from this.
You're right.
All of this.
'Cause, you know, you're
learning from the best.
[Terry] ♪ Back in town
♪ Look out, old Mack is back
[crowd cheering and applauding]
[Peter] Let's hear it again.
Ten out of ten. Ten out of ten.
[Robbie VO] Seeing my dad
surrounded by the
stars of yesteryear
galvanised my need
to become famous.
But I had a more
immediate problem.
What's Mum going to be like
when I tell her I
failed my exams?
Fucked up the rest of my life.
- Did you have a good time?
- Yeah. Smashing.
- How is he?
- Great.
I, erm...
I've got something to tell you.
So have I.
- I failed...
- You're in that band.
What?
You got in! You're
in that band.
[Robbie yelling] Yes!
[Robbie VO] And I
never had to tell her
I failed my exams - until now.
[Robbie chuckling] Sorry, Mum.
[garbage bin crashes]
- [man] Shut up, you tit!
- Oh, fuck off, Glen!
[dog barks]
- Mother!
- [Janet laughs]
- [upbeat music]
- [Robbie howling like a monkey]
[Robbie VO] Nigel
was my introduction
to the adult world.
He was fucking terrifying,
like Willy Wonka.
But what did I care?
I was 15, I was going to
have four older brothers,
and we were going to
take over the world.
Howard Donald, panelbeater.
If you got a dent on your car,
Howard would pound it out.
Jason Orange was
a featured dancer
on a genre-defining
TV music show
called 'The Hit Man and Her'.
["Candy" by Robbie
Williams playing]
Mark Owen...
Little Marco was... lovely.
And then of course...
[angelic musical flourish]
[Nigel] Come here, you.
[Robbie VO] There
was Gary Barlow,
and my first thought was,
who's this dickhead
in those trainers?
They are so three years ago.
[piano plays]
Gary was a genius.
An actual genius.
♪ Once upon a time I
was falling in love... ♪
[Robbie VO] He'd been playing
the working men's clubs
since he was 12 years old
and was earning more
money than his teachers.
♪ There's nothing I can do
♪ A total eclipse
of the heart ♪
[Robbie VO] Trouble was -
Gary sang like an angel,
but he danced like a twat.
["It Only Takes a
Minute" playing]
[choreographer] Seven,
eight. Hit! Hit!
You gotta bring the
energy. Come on!
...seven, eight. Foot and...
[Robbie VO] I recall thinking
two things that day -
a fifth of the spotlight is
better than nothing, and...
...if anyone from
Stoke sees me,
I'm fucking dead.
[people chattering and laughing]
Tikka masalas all round,
no coriander for the boys.
- [Nigel] Thank you.
- No coriander?
[Robbie VO] Whenever Nigel
took us out for dinner,
he would always say...
- I'll put this on your account.
- [chuckling]
[Robbie VO] He wasn't
joking. He recouped it all.
Look around the table, go on.
In five years, we're all
going to hate each other.
- But we'll be fucking rich.
- [all laughing]
Now, first things first.
We work up our act, we
take it on the road.
What about a record deal?
Well, that will come, we'll
get your demo sent out,
we'll let the bidding war begin.
- Ah, but...
- Yes.
Before that, let's shore
up your backstories.
Mark and Jason, you were in a
breakdancing group together.
Gary and Howard, you were in
a band called The Cutest Rush.
Was I the lead?
You weren't then, my
chicken, and you're not now.
- [all laughing]
- Fuck off!
Robert, you had a bit
part in 'Brookside'.
Oh, I was fucking
great, wasn't I?
You were a bit much, frankly.
[all laughing]
Nige, can't we just
say I'm a songwriter?
I've got a ton of lyrics.
Well, I can hold my
breath for two minutes
but I'm not trying to be
a fucking submarine, am I?
[boys laughing]
[Robbie imitates their laughing]
Gary writes the songs, yeah?
You lot toe the line.
Oh, and also, your name's not
Robert anymore - it's Robbie.
[Howard] Oh, tuck in, lads.
[Robbie VO] I fucking
hated the name Robbie,
but it was the single best
thing Nigel did for me.
Robbie became a character.
Something I could hide behind.
Oh, now, the name of the band?
[Howard] Oh, Nige,
I've got a good one.
Kick It!
That's fucking awful.
[all laughing]
I've already got the
name and it's brilliant.
And clench!
[all] Take That!
[Nigel] Oh!
[Robbie VO] Initially,
Nigel's plan was for us to be
a band for the gay scene.
- Alright!
- ♪ La-la-la-la-la!
[Nigel] Let's do this. Just
remember what you rehearsed.
- Robbie, you alright?
- [Nigel] Don't be nervous.
- You all look amazing.
- Light 'em up.
[Nigel] Robbie, what
you doing? Hurry up.
Don't keep 'em waiting.
[Robbie VO] Now, for
years, people have rumoured
about my sexuality.
The worst one was that
all my gay friends
have slept with me
and said I was crap.
I'm not bothered they
said I slept with them.
[Nigel] These are my boys!
[Robbie VO] It's me being
'crap' I'm worried about.
[Nigel] Play it loud!
["I Found Heaven" by
Take That playing]
♪ Woah, woah, woah, woah,
woah, yeah, woah, yeah ♪
♪ I thought I found love
with somebody else's girl ♪
♪ Yeah
♪ Walking 'round feeling
so broken-hearted ♪
♪ Lost in a different world
[Robbie VO] That night, I
discovered a wonderland.
It was welcoming
and non-judgmental.
I'd found my people.
I'd found the promised land.
[Robbie VO] For the entire
first eighteen months,
we made 180 pounds, each.
We played gay club
after gay club.
Two a night.
Until out of nowhere,
Nigel booked us a
club full of girls.
- ♪ Oh...
- [girls scream]
♪ I see heaven in
your eyes with me ♪
♪ Oh, baby
♪ Now I will give my
loving faithfully ♪
[music becomes distorted]
[Robbie's inner voice]
You gonna fucking listen!
Fucking useless prick.
I'm warning you!
♪ Heaven, sweet heaven, baby
♪ On the wings of love
♪ I found heaven, sweet
♪ Heaven sent you
straight to me ♪
♪ My sweet, sweet baby
[crowd cheering and screaming]
- What?!
- Whoo!
What the fuck?!
[crowd screaming]
Oh!
[boys cheering]
[boys whooping]
Yeah!
- Did you hear that?
- [Nigel] Alright.
Settle down. Settle down.
Will you lot shut up?!
I felt like Elvis,
but thin. Ha ha!
[Nigel] I've got good news!
- Good news.
- Good news?
We've had some interest
from a few record labels...
- Oh, fuck off!
- ...in London.
- Oh!
- London! Yes!
- That's absolutely fantastic!
- Yes!
- Thank you so much.
- [Nigel] Yeah, you deserve it.
- You've all done really well.
- Yes! Yes!
[boys laugh]
Except for one of ya.
[boy] Ooh.
We all know who
that is, don't we?
Robbie talked to
a local reporter.
"We're like the A-team. I'm
the sexy, talented one."
Who the fuck gave you...
I didn't know she
was a reporter, Nige.
You know, I almost
started to like you,
but you've fucking
ended that, haven't ya?
- Fuck off!
- What was that?
I think, uh, Robbie's developing
a sense of humour, Nige.
[all laughing]
You think it'd be difficult
to go to Stoke-on-Trent,
get another scally with ratty
hair and call him Robbie?
Right, the club wants us
to do a meet-and-greet.
There's going to be
lots of girls in here,
so let's get one thing clear -
keep it in your pants.
No touching.
- No telephone numbers.
- What?
- No dating.
- No touching?
- Seriously?
- Ever!
- Nige?!
What's the point of
bringing them up here
- if we can't touch them?
- [Nigel] Let's get this done.
- Alright! Bring 'em up!
- Nige!
[young women screaming]
- [loud screaming continues]
- Hi.
I love you all!
[Robbie VO] Nigel had
many rules for Take That,
and the most important was that
we always appeared attainable.
Safe sex is important...
[Robbie VO] He even made
us do a Safer Sex tour
for the Family
Planning Association.
[Mark] So, remember...
[all] Don't be a
fool, cover his tool.
["Be My Lover" by
La Bouche playing]
[Robbie VO] Naturally,
I took it all to heart.
Oh, I love the way
you move, Gary.
[Robbie VO] I was happy to
play Gary for the moment.
Wow.
I'll never wash my hands again.
[Robbie moaning]
- Oh, my God!
- Yeah?
Oh, my God, Hurry
up, hurry up! Quick!
- Oh, that's it.
- Gary, I already stopped.
[Robbie VO] And there it was,
the one time in Nigel's life
he wasn't the biggest
wanker in the room.
[Robbie moaning]
[Robbie sighs]
[executive] Right.
Straight up.
There's no appetite, want
or need for boybands.
They died a death.
It's all grunge now.
[balls clink]
- Did you hear our demo?
- Yes.
[balls clink]
These boys are going to
take this country by storm.
And if you don't
sign them right now,
I'll take them to another label
and you'll be the twat that
let the biggest band in history
slip through your
pudgy fucking fingers.
[clinking stops]
You won't do any of that,
'cause everyone else said no.
I only agreed to see you
because my daughter
saw you boys live,
and she's obsessed.
She assures me that you
are amazing in the flesh.
So...
...I'm going to take a punt that
you're right about these boys.
Now, which one of you is Gary?
That's me, I'm Gary.
["Rock DJ" by Robbie
Williams playing]
[woman] Oh!
♪ Me with the floorshow
♪ Kickin' with your torso
♪ Boys getting high and
the girls even more so ♪
♪ Wave your hands if
you're not with a man ♪
♪ Can I kick it?
[Yes, you can] ♪
♪ I got [funk], you got
[soul] We got everybody ♪
♪ I've got the gift Gonna
stick it in the goal ♪
♪ It's time to move your body
♪ Babylon back in business
Can I get a witness? ♪
♪ Every girl, every man
[ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh] ♪
♪ Houston, do you hear me?
♪ Ground control,
can you feel me? ♪
♪ Need permission to land
♪ I don't want to rock, DJ
♪ But you're making
me feel so nice ♪
♪ When's it gonna stop, DJ?
♪ 'Cause you're keeping
me up all night ♪
[Robbie] Let's go, boys!
- Whoa!
- [boys] Whoa!
[crashing]
♪ Singin' in the classes
♪ Music for your masses
♪ Give no head No
backstage passes ♪
♪ Have a proper giggle
I'll be quite polite ♪
♪ But when I rock the mic
I rock the mic [right] ♪
♪ You got no love, then
you're with the wrong man ♪
[playing through headphones]
♪ It's time to move your body
♪ If you can't get a girl
but your best friend can ♪
♪ It's time to
move your body ♪
♪ I don't want to be sleazy
Baby, just tease me ♪
♪ Got no family planned
[ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh] ♪
♪ Houston, do you hear me?
♪ Ground control,
can you feel me? ♪
♪ Need permission to land
♪ I don't want to
rock [rock], DJ [DJ] ♪
♪ But you're making
me feel so nice ♪
♪ When's it gonna stop, DJ? ♪
♪ 'Cause you're keeping
me up all night ♪
♪ Pimpin' ain't easy
Most of them fleece me ♪
♪ Every night
Yeah! Oh! Oh!
♪ Pimpin' ain't easy
♪ But if you're sellin' it
[sellin' it, sellin' it] ♪
♪ It's alright
Come on!
♪ I don't want to rock
♪ But you're making
me feel so nice ♪
♪ When it's going
to stop, DJ? ♪
♪ 'Cause you're keeping
me up all night ♪
♪ I don't want to rock ♪
[piano solo]
♪ But you're making
me feel so... ♪
♪ You're making
me feel so nice ♪
♪ I don't want to rock, DJ
♪ But you're making
me feel so nice ♪
♪ When it's going
to stop, DJ? ♪
♪ 'Cause you're keeping
me up all night ♪
♪ I don't want to rock
♪ But you're making
me feel so nice ♪
♪ When it's going
to stop, DJ? ♪
♪ 'Cause you're keeping
me up all night ♪
[cheering and cameras clicking]
Every day, there's a new lot.
The coach brings them in.
They come into the garden,
they nick the wood
off the fence,
the clothes off the line.
Someone should do
something about this.
Mum, they want this to happen.
I went down the post
office the other day
and someone called
me a posh slag.
Oh, love, you're not posh.
It's not funny. I can't
make my deliveries anymore.
I'm having to shut
the business, Robert.
Guess who's recording the
lead vocals for our new song?
Mm-hm.
I'll get us out of this shithole
and buy us a fortress,
just like Gary.
And why would I want a
bigger house to hide in?
[girls screaming]
[Robbie VO] That
was the first time
my mum closed the curtains.
I'm going to bed.
If they'll let me.
[Robbie VO] She didn't open
them for another ten years.
[Betty] Hey, love...
Where's my little Robert gone?
I'm a pop star now.
Fat little Robert isn't going
to sell any albums, is he?
I'm just giving the
people what they want.
[crowd screaming]
[cameras clicking]
[Robbie] I go onstage
and act like a gladiator
and I pretend that the whole
world is lucky to see me.
And they all act accordingly.
They don't see what I see.
[Nan] Then stop!
See, that's the
craziest thing to me.
I can't.
[young woman] We
love you, Robbie!
[upbeat frantic music]
[crowd screaming]
[exhales]
[kissing]
Now, fuck off!
I'm here at Take That HQ
with the man responsible
for the band's success,
Nigel Martin Smith.
It's quite a display.
It is, yeah, yeah, we got
Take That dolls,
Take That calendars,
Take That pillows, so you
can sleep with Take That.
[chuckling] I'm just kidding.
Probably cut that bit out.
Uh, for our ethnic fans, we
have Take That Babushka dolls.
Uh, Robbie's inside
Mark, who's inside Jason.
Jason's inside Howard and
they all fit snugly in Gary.
[reporter] Hmm,
that's quite cute.
[Gary] Lyrics?
[Robbie] Just some ideas.
[Gary] Well, come on
then. Give us a look.
- Will I get a credit?
- I don't know.
Are they any good?
- Wouldn't you like to know?
- [Howard] Fuck off.
[Jason] You've got
it all over you.
- [Howard] Fuck off, Jason.
- [Gary] Whatever.
[Jason] Hey. At least
pretend to give a toss.
- What, about all this?
- [Jason] Yeah.
[Robbie] Are you kidding?
Do you have any idea how
naff people think we are?
Oh, fuck off, Robbie,
they bloody love us.
Do you think Oasis
does this shit?!
We need to branch out.
Write something that's not
so fucking cringeworthy.
- And this coming from you.
- Uh...
The one who only shines
when the light's on him.
- [Mark] Alright, Gaz.
- No, no, let him speak.
You think you can just turn up,
scribble some worthless shit
and get your name next to
mine in the song credits?
You add nothing to this.
Any of it.
[music playing]
♪ Turn back the time 'til the
days when our love was new ♪
♪ Do you remember?
♪ No matter what was happening
I was there with you... ♪
Ah, just ah, hold it there
for a second, thanks, Robbie.
[Robbie] That was better, yeah?
Ah, you're... you're still
a little behind, I'm afraid.
Oh, I've always liked
a little behind.
Uh, what we might do, Robbie,
is, um, if we record it -
we can just record it
line by line, yeah?
And we can just stitch
it together later.
Nah, I can do it all at once.
Yeah, let's just, um,
let's just go again.
Yeah, let's go. I got
it. [clears throat]
Sure thing, then. Uh...
- [music plays]
- Here we go.
♪ Turn back the time 'til the
days when our love was new ♪
♪ Do you remember?
♪ No matter what was happening
I was there with you ♪
♪ A ha ♪
♪ But if we all stand
up for what we believe ♪
♪ And maybe live within
our possibilities ♪
[Robbie's inner voice]
You're worthless.
You can't do what Gary does.
They're all laughing at ya.
♪ So, baby, don't
turn away, listen... ♪
Ah, that's... that's great.
Thanks. Thanks, Robbie.
Just give us one wee sec, yeah?
[Robbie whispering] Fuck me.
[Robbie breathing heavily]
[no audio]
I think we might
have it there, mate.
Thank you.
[Robbie inhales deeply]
- Okay, great.
- Let's go, guys.
- Hey.
- Whoo!
Yeah, yeah. Cheers.
Cheers, Robbie.
[Nigel] Give it a sec, Gary,
before you head in there.
- [Nigel] Oh, my God.
- [Gary] You did your best.
[Nigel] Yeah, you know, and
now I feel like the bad guy.
["Relight My Fire"
intro playing]
[men laughing]
[Gary singing] ♪
Turn back the time...
[Howard] Gary Barlow,
ladies and gentlemen!
[applauding]
[Nigel] It's already good.
Fucking hell, the difference!
[man] It's like night
and day, isn't it?
[Nigel] Yeah. Thank you.
Oh, this is a hit.
[Robbie VO] I didn't know it
but I was suffering
from depression.
I hate that phrase -
'suffering from depression'.
It sounds so Scarlett O'Hara -
"I do declare, Mr. Butler,
"I have been suffering
with a bout of depression."
'Clinically
depressed' is better.
Way more lab coaty.
- Dad!
- Here he is! Here he is!
I didn't know you were...
[girl screaming] Oh, my God!
[Peter] I told you, didn't I?
You owe me a pint, love.
- Can I get a photo?
- Of course you can.
I'll take it for you.
Okay, here we go.
- Say 'fuzzy pickle'.
- Fuzzy pickle.
- [Peter] Ah... [laughs]
- [Robbie] Lovely.
Thank you so much.
Did you want one with me in it?
Great idea, yeah!
Yeah, course you do. Come on.
Look at that, eh?
Peas in a pod.
[Peter chuckling]
Can I lose you... use
you... Can I use your loo?
Yeah.
It's a number two.
Be my guest.
- [girl] Oh, my God!
- Yeah... Oh.
[Peter chuckles]
[woman squeals and giggles]
- [door closes]
- She seems nice.
Oh, yeah, terrific. Terrific!
You know they've cordoned off
the whole street, don't ya?
- [girls screaming]
- There's girls everywhere.
They're not playing nice either.
It's like a bloodsport
out there. [chuckles]
I told the security
lads you were my son.
- I nearly got torn apart.
- [Robbie chuckles]
You in town for long?
No, no, just... just passing
through. Back home tonight.
After I collect my
pint. [chuckles]
I wish I'd known
you were coming.
- What's this?
- Nothing.
Prozac?
What have you got to mope about?
You boys are flying.
Bloody Brits nomination...
I've been telling
everyone about that.
I know. It's just...
It's all a bit
overwhelming, Dad, you know?
It's like I can't keep
track of who I am anymore.
Well, go and ask
that lot out there.
They know exactly who you are.
The other lads you'd
be hard-pressed
to pick 'em out of
a police line-up.
Well, not Gary, obviously,
'cause he's the creative one,
but, uh, you...
...you're living
the dream, youth.
[girl screaming from
outside] We love you, Robbie.
How can you not
know who you are...
...when there are thousands
of people screaming your name?
[toilet flushing]
[screaming crowd]
[distorted audio]
- [thudding]
- [Mark] Jesus! Rob!
- [Nigel] What did he take?
- [Howard] Could be anything.
[Nigel] Hold the
show until I say.
- [Howard] No, no, no, no!
- You were an afterthought.
Couldn't sing, couldn't dance.
Looks... five at best.
Everything you have,
everything, I've given you.
And you don't deserve any of it.
[loud music starting]
[Howard] Oh, fucking hell!
[roaring crowd] [loud music]
- Are you fucking retarded?!
- I fucking told them...
- Alright! Get in position.
- [Gary] Fucking hell, Nige!
- I said, get in position, now!
- Get up, get up!
[crowd roaring] [intro
to "Relight My Fire"]
Wake up, you fucking baby!
[Gary] Right, follow my lead!
[Robbie VO] All of this
because of a fucking wink.
[crowd roaring]
[Gary singing] ♪ Help me escape
this feeling of insecurity ♪
♪ Ah, ah
♪ I need you so much
♪ But I don't think
you really need me ♪
♪ Ah, ah
♪ But if we all stand
up in the name of love ♪
♪ And state the case of
what we're dreaming of ♪
♪ I've got to say I
only dream of you ♪
♪ But like a thief
in the night ♪
♪ You took away the
love that I knew ♪
♪ Oh, oh-ho-ho-ho
♪ Relight my fire
- ♪ Your love is my
only desire - [screams]
♪ Relight my fire
♪ 'Cause I need your love
Oh!
[Robbie] Whoo! Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Passed out! That's a new low.
It was a dodgy curry.
Your job is simple -
sing the harmonies
and toe the line.
You'd like that, wouldn't ya?
[Gary] Know your place.
You're making us look
like fucking idiots.
- Ah! Hoo!
- [crowd cheering]
♪ Turn back the times
to the days when ♪
- [Robbie] Oh, fuck!
- ♪ Our love was new
♪ Do you remember?
♪ No matter what was happening
I was there with... ♪
[Robbie singing] ♪ You
- [crowd roaring]
- [Robbie] ♪ A ha...
♪ But if we all stand
up for what we believe ♪
♪ And maybe live within
our possibilities ♪
♪ The world would be
wild for the dream ♪
♪ So, baby, don't turn away
♪ Listen to what
I gotta say, ah ♪
[crowd] ♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
♪ Relight my fire
♪ 'Cause I need...
♪ Oh, I need...
♪ Your love
[song ends]
[crowd roaring]
["Could It Be Magic"
begins] [crowd roaring]
♪ Sun
[Robbie VO] Because he
writes all the songs,
Gary makes all the money.
He's got a mansion in
the north of England
with a driveway full of cars.
- Fuck me!
- [engine stops]
[Robbie VO] And a butler.
While I'm still living at Mum's.
He's Elton now.
[snorts]
[Robbie VO] And they're all
waiting for me in the garden.
And it's to talk
about the problem.
- And I am the problem.
- Whoo!
[squeaking rope]
Robbie, so, um...
Well, we've all been
having a think, and, um,
we'd quite like to do
the next tour as a, ah...
...as a four-piece.
[Mark] Just to see
if we can do it.
[Jason] Yeah. To
see if we can do it.
[Howard] Perhaps
you could focus on
some of that solo material
you've been working on or, um...
[Gary] To be honest, Rob,
we've been doing it as a
four-piece for a while.
I think you should.
Is that it, then?
Uh... Yeah.
[Robbie] Wheeee!
[bird caws]
Can I take this?
Yeah, Rob. If you want.
[Robbie grunting]
This is it!
This... is... the end!
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
[softly chuckling]
[seatbelt clicks]
[low tense music]
[engine starting erratically]
Hmm!
[car backfires]
- Fuck!
- [engine idling]
[car accelerating]
[glass shattering]
[Robbie singing] ♪ So
unimpressed but so in awe
♪ Such a saint Such a whore ♪
♪ So self-aware
So full of shit ♪
♪ So indecisive So adamant ♪
♪ I'm contemplating
thinking about thinking ♪
♪ It's overrated Just
get another drink in ♪
[people chatter]
♪ Watch me come undone
♪ They're selling razor blades
and mirrors in the streets ♪
[fans screaming]
- ♪ I pray that - [horn honks]
♪ When I'm coming down
you'll be asleep ♪
[fans screaming]
♪ If I ever hurt you, your
revenge will be so sweet ♪
♪ Because I'm scum
and I'm your son ♪
[truck honking]
[tyres skidding]
♪ I come undone
[Radio announcer]
Fans are still reeling
from the announcement on Monday
that Robbie Williams
has split from Take That.
Help Line switchboards, set
up after reports of suicides,
have been flooded by
tearful Take That fans...
[Radio announcer] But he
had built up a reputation
as a party animal...
♪ So rock'n'roll So
corporate suits ♪
♪ So damn ugly So damn cute ♪
♪ So well-trained
- [horn honks]
- ♪ So animal
♪ So need-your-love
So fuck-you-all ♪
[horn honks]
♪ I'm not scared of dying
I just don't want to ♪
♪ If I stopped lying I'd
just disappoint you ♪
♪ I come undone
♪ They're selling razor blades
and mirrors in the street ♪
[car accelerating]
[dramatic music]
♪ I pray that when I'm coming
down you'll be asleep ♪
[music crescendos
and then softens]
[crowd singing together on bus]
♪ If I ever hurt you, your
revenge will be so sweet ♪
♪ Because I'm scum
but I'm your son ♪
♪ I come un...
- [tyres screeching]
- [Robbie gasping]
[water bubbling]
[low tense music]
[fangirl] How
could you do this?
[fangirl] We need you, Robbie!
[fangirl] Don't go!
[fangirl] Robbie, don't do this!
[fangirl] Don't leave!
[echoes of sobbing girls]
[underwater muted audio]
Hmm? Hmm?
[Robbie VO] The cheeky
member of Take That
is now the fucked-up messy one
who's gone and
broken up the band.
And people hate me for it.
But really, they're only saying
what I think about myself.
[screams]
I've a raging cocaine habit,
I'm a full-blown alcoholic
and I'm twenty-one.
[ice shattering]
I think I was always going to
be an alcoholic or an addict.
I just had the money and the
means to get there quicker.
[cameras clicking]
[Robbie VO] But I'm also
incredibly competitive.
I mean, I've no idea
how I'm going to pull
off a solo career.
But there's an
energy to revenge,
and it's very, very seductive.
[crowd] Ten, nine,
eight, seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
Happy New Year!
[all cheering]
[fireworks exploding]
[cheering]
[upbeat music playing]
[kisses]
[crowd chattering]
It's going to happen.
No ifs, no buts. No left, no
right. Just straight ahead.
[sighing]
I'm going to be fucking massive.
[woman] A massive what?
Fuck! You scared
the shit out of me.
You said you wanted
to be massive?
Ah, well, I was just, um...
...wishing for a
little extra girth.
[chuckling]
- What is it you do?
- Oh, yeah...
[woman] Oh sorry, should
I already know that?
No, no, no, no, no. Um...
No, I'm... I'm a
singer and songwriter.
Really?
Yeah. Yeah, just
starting out on my own.
I was in Take That and...
The boyband?
[laughing]
Oh, don't mind me.
Sorry.
No, you're alright. I
mean, it is why I left.
Dancing around in the background
like a camp sadomasochist.
I mean, if I'm going
to look like a tosser,
I might as well do
it down stage centre.
So it's all about the spotlight?
Wow, not even any
lube. Just full fist.
I'm just saying -
if you're gonna start
out on your own,
you might as well
be honest about why.
- Shit, are you a journalist?
- Fuck, no.
I'm just curious.
I'm not sure you'd understand.
Try me.
[flings bottle]
You know, I was given
the golden ticket
but it felt like I
was bound and gagged
for the last five years.
And not in a hot way, either.
In like a battery to
the scrotum sort of way.
[laughing]
I don't know, sexy,
mysterious, masked lady.
[woman chuckles]
I guess I've just
reached a point
where I want to prove I
can make it on my own.
Prove to who?
Everyone.
See? I told you you
wouldn't understand.
[woman chuckles]
Oh, fuck me!
[both laughing]
- [Robbie VO] Nicole Appleton.
- ♪ I know where it's at
[Robbie VO] She and
her sister were members
of the girl band, All Saints.
Their manager was a cunt, too.
She was absolutely lovely -
with the single
worst taste in men.
Yeah, you alright?
[Nicole] Fame is so
fucking weird, isn't it?
[chuckles]
It's like that uneasy
feeling you get
when they bring the cake out
and the whole restaurant
sings "Happy Birthday" to you
and you can't wait until "Happy
Birthday" stops being sung.
I mean, people are doing
a really nice thing,
but you just want it
to stop so you can...
Eat the fucking cake.
Yeah.
[chuckling]
Well, now you've
got your gag off,
what are you going to say?
- I've got some lyrics.
- Oh...
I mean, they're
basically different takes
on how much I hate myself.
Oh, so a Christmas album then?
[Robbie laughing]
I'm not sure about an album.
You know, at the moment,
I'd just like to
write one good song.
[laughs]
- You're overthinking it.
- Hmm?
Just write about
whatever's in front of you.
Look...
♪ I've got a boat but
mine's made of rubber ♪
♪ I cut a hole in the back
♪ And use my cock as a rudder
[laughs]
[Robbie] Yes! It's a hit!
See? You're going to
be massive in no time.
[laughs]
♪ I was her
♪ She was me
♪ We were one
♪ We were free
♪ If there's somebody
calling me on ♪
♪ She's the one
[lush orchestral arrangement]
♪ If there's somebody
♪ Calling me on
♪ She's the one
[Nicole] ♪ We were young
♪ We were wrong
♪ We were fine all along ♪
[both] ♪ If there's somebody
♪ Calling me on
♪ She's the one
[both] ♪ When you get
to where you wanna go ♪
♪ And you know the
things you wanna know ♪
♪ You're smiling
[Nicole] ♪ When you said
what you wanna say ♪
♪ And you know the
way you wanna play ♪
[both] ♪ You'll be so high ♪
♪ You'll be flying
♪ Though the sea
♪ Will be strong
♪ I know we'll carry on
♪ 'Cause if there's somebody
♪ Calling me on
[Nicole] ♪ He's the one
[Robbie] ♪ If there's
somebody calling me on ♪
♪ She's the one
[both] ♪ When you get
to where you wanna go ♪
♪ And you know the
things you wanna know ♪
♪ You're smiling
♪ When you said
what you wanna say ♪
♪ And you know the way
you wanna play it ♪
♪ You'll be so high
♪ You'll be flying
[no audio]
[gentle orchestral music
plays over dialogue]
[gentle orchestral
music continues]
♪ She's the one
♪ He's the one
[Nicole sighing]
[Robbie singing softly]
♪ You can't
manufacture a miracle ♪
♪ The silence was pitiful...
[people chattering]
[man] It's not... It's
not a competition, girls.
It's just hard work.
You need to put that in.
♪ Do a little dance...
[Nate] Here. [puts glass down]
This place is posh as fuck.
You know, I've just seen
fucking Bono in the toilet.
Had a look.
Tiny.
[Nate laughing]
You've missed me, haven't you?
Ah, of course you have.
Hmm! Hey, so...
You know my
girlfriend, Kayleigh?
- Kayleigh.
- The one with the clubfoot?
No, she ain't got a clubfoot.
- Well...
- No. Her pelvis is out.
Anyway, she's... up the duff.
I'm going to be a dad.
That's amazing.
I'm just surprised the
little thing still works.
Fuck off!
Shut up! Shut up! Here it is.
[TV announcer]
The wait is over!
Coming in at number one,
it's new, it's brilliant,
it's "Never Ever" by All Saints.
[screaming with joy]
[people applauding]
["Never Ever" playing
in background]
[Nicole laughs excitedly]
Whoo!
Come on! [laughs]
[kissing]
- I can't believe it!
- Well done, babe.
- You deserve it.
- It'll be your turn next.
[people cheering]
[man] Nicole, give
us a few words!
[woman] Yes. Nicole.
[scattered applause]
Okay. Ahh, I just...
I can't believe we did it.
- Number fucking one!
- [crowd cheering]
To everyone who has supported
us through the years,
you're family, and we love you.
[people cheering]
- [Nicole] Whoo!
- [cork popping]
[laughs] And to my...
- Ah, to my best friends...
- [snooker balls clack]
[Nicole] Having a
number one is amazing
and getting to celebrate
it together is the best.
[Robbie VO] Liam Gallagher
was the lead singer of Oasis,
the biggest band on the planet.
I'm in love with their songs.
I'm in love with the lyrics.
I'm in love with how
provocative they are.
[snorts]
I'm just totally
in love with them,
and I want to be them.
Fame is a powerful aphrodisiac.
It means even ugly
people can get laid.
[balls clack]
Mind you, guitars do that, too.
What's all that about, then?
Got a number one.
Is that all? Fucking hell.
If I orgasmed every
time I had a number one,
I'd be fucking dry.
Yeah.
- You listen to this cunt?
- Yeah!
Like he fucking knows what
we're fucking talking about.
You want a number one,
you should've stayed
Gary's back-up dancer.
[people laughing]
[Liam] Guess who's had
the largest ever demand
for concert tickets
in British history?
Me.
And the band...
Knebworth, right?
125,000 fucking screaming cunts.
That's insane.
It's how you know you've
made it, fucking knobhead.
[people laughing]
[Robbie VO] Me and Liam
wouldn't always be so cuddly.
Would anybody like
to see me fight Liam?
[crowd cheering]
Liam, a hundred
grand of your money,
a hundred grand of my money.
We'll get in the ring
and we'll have a fight
and you can all watch it on TV.
What do you think about that?
Now are you going to do it
or are you going to pussy
out, you fucking wimp?
[crowd cheering]
[Robbie VO] Thankfully,
he wasn't in the
country at the time.
Knebworth...
[glass shattering]
Come on, let's
go. This is shit.
[cue clatters]
- Nice chatting to you, Noel.
- Fuck off, cunt.
[Liam] Hey, twinkletoes,
you coming or what?
Yeah. Come on.
[crowd exuberantly celebrating]
["Never Ever" by
All Saints playing]
♪ Never ever have I
ever felt so sad ♪
[person] Whoo!
[floor creaking]
[keys jingling]
[Robbie chuckling]
Good evening, Knebworth.
You all look gorgeous tonight.
Here's one from my new album.
Thank you very much.
[fridge shuts]
[Nicole] Hiya.
Fuck me, aren't
you Miss Number One
of the United
Kingdom of Britain?
[laughs]
- Maybe.
- Mm-hm. [kissing]
And where did you end up?
I got kidnapped
by Liam Gallagher.
Oh...
And you looked like you were
having a good enough time.
[laughs]
Anyway, I was just trying
to make sense of it.
Of what?
"Never Ever".
You don't... What? You don't...
You don't like our song?
Oh, it's fine. I mean, I'm not
sure it's a number one, but...
Well, people seem to like it.
It would be nice if my fiancé...
Screaming, jumping around,
making fucking speeches...
And all that bullshit
about family.
It's not bullshit.
It's everything to me.
Right.
So did you tell them that
you gave up our family
to get that number one, then?
Nah.
I bet you left that bit out of
your little speech, didn't you?
[sighs]
You're so fucking ugly
when you're wasted.
Well, I'll be sober tomorrow.
Oh, and won't that be nice!
I can't believe I had to tell
everyone that you left tonight
because something
important came up.
It did.
Getting fucked up
with your mates?
At least they know how to
write a proper number one.
Which is more than you can.
Scribbling lyrics in
your little notebook,
but you're too scared
to show them to anyone.
A number one and she's
giving out the advice.
I didn't ask you to lie to your
friends, 'cause guess what,
I don't give a fuck
what they think!
You give a fuck what
everyone thinks, Rob.
That's all you
give a fuck about.
[plate smashes]
[door slamming]
[Robbie whispers] Dickhead.
[television playing]
[Robbie and Betty laughing]
We need crisps.
We're alright, Nan.
Well, I don't want you
wasting away on me.
They don't have washing
machines in London?
Yeah, but you do it with love.
Oh, you bugger.
You should come home
more often, you know.
She's slowing down.
Rubbish. Nan will
outlive all of us.
Anyway, I'm about
to be very busy.
I rang around and
I've got a meeting
with a producer
called Guy Chambers.
Nicole's got a number one.
Fucking Gary's got number ones.
And here I am turning
into a farmyard animal.
I wouldn't change a
hair on your head.
Bless you, Nan.
[Betty] Now, I
spoke to your dad.
Oh, that makes one of us.
It's been radio silence
since I left the band.
He's agreed to see you again.
Agreed? What do you mean?
Well, to have you visit,
on your school holidays.
He called me, remember?
He said it'd been too long.
He invited me.
Yes, that's right.
I told him to.
[Betty] You see?
- [Betty] Oh, Jesus...
- Oh, Betty.
[Janet] No, no, no.
- [Betty crying] I'm so sorry.
- Oh, Betty.
- [Betty crying]
- No.
[Janet] It's alright.
Hey, Nan, it's alright.
[Janet] Shhh.
Come on. Don't cry.
- It's alright.
- [Betty cries]
- [Janet] Shhh, Betty.
- [Betty] I'm so sorry, love.
[Janet] It's alright, duck.
I'm sorry.
[Betty sobbing]
[Robbie rapping] ♪ My
rhyme's complex, yes!
♪ You're just picking
up giro cheques, bless ♪
♪ A whole life for the YTS, oh
♪ I line up in a line
of nine suspects ♪
♪ And I wine and dine
the fine witness ♪
♪ Then she reclines and
resigns to my wish list ♪
♪ So I pop it out
like the litmus test ♪
♪ And she's like, am I
allowed to lick this yet... ♪
Okay, okay! Hang
on, hang on. Ugh.
Listen, I appreciate
you coming over,
but this isn't going to work.
[Robbie VO] Guy Chambers.
Guy likes it when I talk
about the holidays we shared,
and I like it when he agrees
to let me sing our songs.
[Guy] You don't mind, do you?
[Robbie] So our
lawyers had a chat...
And here we are on a beach.
[Guy] Uh, lower...
You've only heard half of them.
And they're all the same.
I can't even tell when one
ends and the next one begins.
It's like you've written lyrics
you think other
people want to hear.
I don't know...
That might be okay
in a boyband...
So you want me to get
naked on the first date?
Well, it's the only
way this works.
Songs are only valuable if
they cost you something.
Luckily, I'm always
naked on the first date.
If you're going to laugh,
do it on the inside, yeah?
I dent easily.
Can you give me a C?
[Guy plays chord]
[Robbie nervously
singing] ♪ You can't...
[whispering] Fuck me.
Better make it a B flat.
[Guy playing piano chord]
♪ You can't
manufacture a miracle ♪
♪ The silence was pitiful
♪ That day
♪ And love is
getting too cynical ♪
♪ Passion's just physical
♪ These days
♪ You analyse
everyone you meet ♪
♪ But get no sign
♪ Loving kind
♪ Every night you admit defeat
♪ And cry yourself blind
[clearing throat] Ah,
this is the chorus.
♪ If you can't wake
up in the morning ♪
♪ 'Cause your bed
lies vacant at night ♪
♪ If you're lost, hurt
♪ Tired or lonely
♪ Something beautiful
will come your way ♪
And the second verse.
♪ The DJ...
No, no! No! Hang on, hang on.
Um...
We have to double the
chorus or it'll sound crap.
What was that list? Lost...
♪ ..hurt, tired or lonely...
Right, that's the
hook. That's the gold.
The 'something beautiful' bit
is cream on top. You've got...
♪ Lost, hurt, tired or lonely
[humming with piano]
[Guy] And then you
repeat. You understand?
- Yeah.
- Right.
Pick it up from the chorus,
and, you know,
give it some welly.
Even if it's shit, you
got to make it your shit.
[Guy] Two, three...
♪ If you can't wake
up in the morning ♪
♪ 'Cause your bed
lies vacant at night ♪
♪ If you're lost,
hurt, tired or lonely ♪
♪ Can't control it
Try as you might ♪
[Guy] There you go!
♪ May you find that love
that won't leave you ♪
♪ May you find it by
the end of the day ♪
♪ You won't be lost,
hurt, tired or lonely ♪
♪ Something beautiful
will come your way ♪
One more time.
♪ Something beautiful
♪ Will come your way
[sings high note]
You're not as crap as I thought.
Thanks.
We need to clean it up
a bit but it's a start.
Now, what else have
you got in there?
[jingle plays] ♪ Radio Wave...
And coming up we have a
surprise guest in the studio.
It's none other than
ex-Take That bad boy,
Robbie Williams!
[Robbie snorts]
[Robbie VO] Chris Briggs
- manager to the stars.
Amazingly, he saw
something in me.
I mean, besides monstrous
amounts of drugs and booze.
[Briggs] It'll be
nice and intimate.
Fifty people or so
- contest winners,
so they'll be super excited.
And just remember
it's going out live,
so mind your
'shits' and 'fucks'.
You should start with a cover,
something people recognise.
We want them to
recognise our songs.
And they will, but you
have to woo them first.
You gotta get me to Knebworth.
[Briggs] How about you
get through this one
without giving yourself
a heart attack?
Just get me there, alright?
[Briggs] Baby steps, mate.
Look, I know this isn't
much of a gig, but...
Oh, I don't know.
Blackpool, Knebworth... Hi!
Plus, we need the air time.
What have you got to lose?
I would've said my dignity
but Take That already
stole it, so...
I mean it, Briggsy, I have
got to play Knebworth.
Whatever it takes.
It'll take everything.
Sure you're ready for that?
[sharp inhale]
Then make every
performance count.
Light 'em up.
- [applause]
- One, two, three, four.
[plays song intro]
♪ You got to know how to
pony Like Bony Maronie ♪
- ♪ Do the mashed potato
- [audience laughs]
♪ Do the alligator
[audience chuckles]
♪ Put your hands on your hips
♪ Let your backbone slip
♪ Do the watusi [kisses]
♪ Like my little Lucy
♪ Na-na-na-na-na
na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na ♪
[music distorting]
[Robbie's inner voice]
You're going to die!
[radio reporter] You've
left the safety of the band
and now you're going
out on your own.
How does that feel?
[Robbie on radio] I
couldn't be happier.
I'm finally free, you know,
and this is only the beginning.
[Robbie] Come on!
[rock song intro playing]
[radio announcer] Well, the
first punches have been thrown
and it's Gary Barlow
at number one...
Light 'em up.
...while Robbie's first
album, "Life Thru A Lens",
has debuted at number eleven.
- Robbie's fate now rests...
- [snorts] Oh!
...on a national
charm offensive tour.
[exhales deeply]
[announcer] Lock
up your daughters,
lock up your sons.
It's Robbie Williams!
[applause and cheering]
[Robbie] You know
what I need you to do!
One, two, three, four.
♪ Na-na-na-na-na
na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na ♪
♪ Na-na-na-na
- ♪ Na...
- [music distorts]
[Robbie's inner voice] I'm
gonna rip your fucking eyes out!
[TV interviewer]
With his new album...
Come on! ...rocketing
up the charts,
ladies and gentlemen,
Robbie Williams!
♪ Na-na-na-na
[radio announcer] Please
welcome Robbie Williams.
[TV announcer] Robbie
Williams, ladies and gentlemen.
[TV interviewer] He's an
internationally loved star...
♪ I said watch me do it
[Robbie] I wanna
sing, goddamnit!
♪ Watch me do it
And I wanna dance.
[Robbie on radio]
Being a pop star means
you can live all your fantasies.
I think it's what's known
as the 'lucky bastard'.
Well, you know, being
in a relationship means
I've put away my shagging boots.
But I know where the closet is.
[interviewer laughs]
♪ Dance with me, honey ♪
♪ Like long tall Sally
[Robbie on radio] You
know the great thing is
I've actually arrived now,
because back... back at home,
I've been voted the
'Rear of the Year'.
[female reporter] Is that
right? You gonna show us?
[male reporter] So it's fair to
say you're box office, right?
[Robbie on TV] I've
got me platinum disc
and then I'm getting a
double platinum disc now.
It means I'm very
famous. [laughs]
♪ One, two,
na-na-na-na-na-na-na ♪
[Robbie's inner voice]
We are coming for you!
You can't write. You haven't
got 'it'. You've got nothing!
[Robbie screaming]
[Robbie's inner voice]
You are fucking dead!
[audience screaming]
[flash lights clicking]
[people shouting]
Move! Move!
Light 'em up!
[cacophony of sounds]
[wheels screech]
[crowd cheering]
- [woman] Robbie!
- Fuck off, the lot of ya!
Fuck off!
[cacophony of sounds]
[retching]
♪ Na-na-na-na-na
[awards presenter] And the
winner is... Robbie Williams.
- [man] Robbie Williams!
- [man] It's Robbie Williams!
[man] And the winner
is Robbie Williams!
- [man] Robbie Williams...
- [woman] Robbie Williams!
[woman] A perfect
end to a great night
for Robbie Williams.
[footsteps] [music pounds]
[Peter] I'm sure you all
recognise this young man,
but did you know he
had a famous father?
No!
[Peter] If any of you
lovely ladies wanna come up
and sit on Santa's knee,
I'll see what I've got
in my sack for you.
[Christmas carol playing]
Rob?!
[cacophony of sounds]
[music playing]
Brrrr.
Light 'em up.
[deep breathing]
Whoa!
[Tom Jones] ♪ You
got mashed potato
[Robbie] ♪ Do the alligator
[Robbie's inner voice] We're
going to peel your skin off.
Slit your throat.
We are going to
fucking murder you!
[Robbie screaming]
♪ Long tall Sally...
[Tom Jones] ♪ Jump back
in the alley, baby ♪
♪ Put your hand on your hip ♪
♪ Oh! Let your backbone slip
[Tom Jones] ♪ Oh, yeah
♪ Oh
♪ Yeah!
[music continues]
[crowd roaring]
[Robbie's inner voice]
Where are you going to run?
Where are you going
to fucking hide?
You useless little prick!
You're going to die
alone, you cunt!
You're fucking replaceable!
You can't escape this!
[making monkey noises
and hyperventilating]
[grunting]
[Peter] Oh, yes, put
it there, son. [laughs]
[music concludes]
[crowd roaring]
[Peter] Fan-bloody-tastic!
- Listen to that. It's deafening.
- [woman] Robbie! Robbie!
[Peter] Oh, thank
you. I'm the dad.
Taught him everything he knows.
Peter Conway. [laughs]
You know what, Chris,
entrances and exits.
No one cares about
that stuff anymore.
But tonight, you outshone
Tom Jones, lad! [laughs]
Oh, look at him. Just
another day at the office.
Well, this is going to
knock your socks off.
Rob! Rob!
Guess who's playing
Knebworth next summer?
[Peter chuckling]
Knebworth! Ha ha!
Wait till I tell the lads!
Hey, have you thought
about a support act?
Now, I could do you
a couple of numbers.
Four at most.
It's incredible.
[Briggs] It also comes
with a new record deal.
It's obscene!
[Peter exclaiming] Yeah-heh-heh!
Look at you! You're
bulletproof. Ha ha!
Oh, I need a drink.
Look at this! Just what
the doctor ordered.
[Briggs] Okay, I'll
leave you to celebrate.
Congratulations.
Thanks, Chris.
Knebworth.
How does it feel?
[softly] Crippling.
- It'll sink in.
- [cork pops]
It's like someone's picked
sides for an after-school game
and it's all gone
horribly, horribly wrong.
I mean, it's...
It's one against thousands.
[Peter] Bollocks! The
audience loves ya.
[quietly] I can't do it.
I can't carry Knebworth. [pants]
I'll be like a lamb to the
fucking slaughter, Dad.
- It's just stage fright.
- You're not listening!
- [Robbie bangs table]
- [Peter] No. It's normal. Okay?
You know what's
always helped me?
A little bit of Dutch courage.
Don't I know it.
Dad, I'm sorry. Dad!
No one buys a ticket to
hear your problems, son.
You wanna know why
these people are gods?
'Cause they make other
people's problems go away.
- Dad, Dad, stay. Please!
- [door opens]
[inhales deeply]
[mobile phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[snorts]
- Whoa!
- [audience cheering]
[sighs]
[giggling]
[audience cheering]
[Parkinson] My next guest
has been climbing the charts
- and conquering the world.
- Here he is!
Ready? Here's daddy's best mate.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Robbie Williams!
[audience applause and cheering]
["Parkinson" theme
music playing]
[Parkinson] Well, this has been
a sudden change in fortune
for you, has it not?
I mean, you're flying high.
Sober as a judge, Parky.
- [audience laughing]
- Well, uh...
Sorry, sorry, I have to
do this. [clears throat]
- Ooh!
- [audience chuckling]
Look, Nan, it's Parky!
[audience laughter]
Oh, Betty! It's Robert.
[Parkinson] Let's
talk if we may
about this success
you've been having.
I mean, it's not the first time,
is it?
You've had it before
with Take That.
Would you say that this is
a different kind of success?
It means a great
deal more to me now.
I'm about to perform in
front of a record crowd
at Knebworth in a few weeks.
- [audience applauding]
- No, no, stop it. It's nothing.
It's only the biggest music
event in British history!
[audience cheering
and applauding]
That's my boy.
But, of course, Knebworth
is not the only record
you've broken recently, is it?
There's the matter of
your new deal with EMI -
eighty million pounds.
- How does that feel?
- [Robbie] Ah, I don't know.
I'm rich beyond
my wildest dreams!
[Robbie VO] I thought
I was quoting that lady
who famously won the lottery.
- But she said...
- Spend, spend, spend!
[Robbie VO] So no one got it.
Mind you, I've said worse
things in interviews.
[cameras clicking]
[reporters shouting]
[man] How would you describe
your time with Take That?
[Robbie] I was very fortunate
to be in Take That...
...and four out of
the five Spice Girls.
- [laughing]
- Posh said no, didn't she?
Uh, now, you've connected
with many women in the past...
Oh, we're going to
talk about my sex life.
- [audience laughter]
- Well, I suppose...
There's nothing to
write home about.
Which is a shame 'cause Mum
loves getting those letters.
[audience laughter]
[Nicole] Oh, I mean,
how many flat
tyres can you have?
- The second one...
- [door shuts]
...we didn't even
get out of the car.
There was no way Natalie
was gonna ruin her hair,
so they just jacked it
up with us all inside.
- [phone ringing]
- And the weather was...
[Robbie] I'm just
popping to the loo.
[Nicole] The weather
was horrendous.
At least the sound was good.
My voice was tired, though.
Probably because
I wasn't sleeping.
Which is weird because the
bed was insanely comfortable.
I even got the name of the
mattress in case we wanted...
[Parkinson] But you're
finally settling down?
[Robbie] I have to be a realist.
You know, we're
both on tour a lot,
and it can be
difficult, you know.
[Nicole quietly gasping]
[Parkinson] So tell me, what's
it like for Robbie Williams
to be in love?
Well, that's difficult too.
Um...
Flings are much easier.
[audience laughing]
[gentle tense music]
You make me feel so small...
...and I've hated you for it...
...for making me feel so...
...unnecessary.
[lighter cover flicks open]
[Nicole] The fucking awful
things you do... [sniffles]
I thought you couldn't help it.
But you just don't want to.
[sniffles]
And I can't help you anymore.
[gentle piano music]
[ring clinks]
[sighing]
Rob?
[water gurgling]
[Nicole] Rob?
Rob, please say something.
[Echoes] Baby...
[Nicole breathing raggedly]
- [grunting]
- [thudding]
- [Robbie] Nic, please!
- You're a fucking animal!
[Robbie] Babe... Babe,
you need to calm down.
[Nicole] Don't tell
me what I need.
[Robbie] Listen...
- [Nicole] Get out!
- [Robbie] I can fix it!
You're too fucking late!
[Robbie] But I love you!
["Something Stupid"
instrumental playing]
[music speeding up] [thudding]
- [thudding]
- [Robbie grunts]
[Briggs] Easy!
Easy now. Come on.
- [Robbie] Briggsy...
- [door opens]
- [Guy] Oh, what the fuck.
- [audience screaming outside]
- He's alright.
- Course I am!
- Shit!
- [door closes]
[Guy] You should've
said 'no' to this one.
[Briggs] To "Top of the Pops"?
You can't buy this
kind of promotion.
[Guy] What's to promote?
Knebworth's sold out.
- [sniffs]
- [Briggs] The world tour.
What, he just does Knebworth
and then he pops his
feet up, does he?
You thought getting
to the top was hard.
- Try staying there.
- [knocking on door]
- [woman] On in five.
- [Briggs] Come on, you're up.
[mobile ringtone plays]
Leave it.
Ooh, it's a woman!
Hi, Mum, I'm about
to go on "Top..."
[Janet on phone]
Where have you been?
- I've been trying to reach you.
- I know, I know, but listen.
I'll have to talk to
you later, ducky head,
because my pianist, well, he's
accidentally shat himself,
and it's just a horror show.
[Janet] It's your nan.
She kept asking for ya.
I tried calling ya, but...
I'm so sorry,
love. She's gone.
[Briggs] Come on,
mate. Let's go.
[solemn choral vocalising]
[Betty] Whoever pulls the
sword out of the stone
gets to be the new
King of England.
[TV presenter] He's
here tonight to sing
what has become the
unofficial national anthem.
It's the song on everyone's
lips and in everyone's hearts.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the ego has landed.
[Betty] So the next
thing you know,
all the knights are straining...
[Betty exclaiming and laughing]
...and turning red.[laughs]
But nobody could budge it.
So you can imagine
how everyone laughed
when little Arthur
stepped up for his turn.
[laughs] Everyone.
Except Merlin.
Merlin just stroked his
beard and whispered,
"Arthur,
"I know those sexy, muscular
knights couldn't do it
"and you're just a
little fart of a child
"with puny little arms.
"But I believe in you."
♪ I sit and wait
[rain falling]
♪ Does an angel
♪ Contemplate my fate?
♪ And do they know the
places where we go ♪
♪ When we're grey and old?
♪ 'Cause I have been told
♪ That salvation
♪ Lets their wings unfold
♪ So when I'm lying in my bed
♪ Thoughts running
through my head ♪
♪ And I feel that
love is dead ♪
♪ I'm loving angels instead
[crowd roaring]
♪ And through it all
[audience members sing along]
♪ She offers me protection
♪ A lot of love and affection
♪ Whether I'm right or wrong
♪ And down the waterfall
♪ Wherever it may take me
♪ I know that life
won't break me ♪
♪ When I come to call
♪ She won't forsake me
♪ I'm loving angels instead
["Angels" musical interlude]
[cameras clicking]
[reporters all shouting]
♪ And through it all
♪ She offers me protection
♪ A lot of love and affection
♪ Whether I'm right or wrong
♪ And down the waterfall
♪ Wherever it may take me
♪ I know that life
won't break me ♪
♪ When I come to call
♪ She won't forsake me
♪ I'm loving angels instead
[Robbie screaming in
rage] [TV shattering]
[cacophony of sounds]
[tense music rising]
[clattering and shattering]
[final strains of
"Angels" playing gently]
[car engine stops]
[glass crunching]
They were out of
salt and vinegar.
I don't want 'em.
Okay.
Hey, we should get
the boys together.
Hey? Have a little knees-up
before your concert tomorrow.
It'd do you good.
I can't face it.
Zip me up. [grunts]
[Nate] Fucking hell.
What time's lift-off?
- It helps hide the fat.
- Oh, yeah.
You've no idea what it
takes to get up there.
- I can't sleep.
- [machine whirring]
My back's fucked.
Yeah, but once you're up there,
you're smashing it, so...
See, that fucks me right
off when people say that.
Being up there's the worst bit.
Pays alright, though. [chuckles]
Fuck.
[machine whirring continues]
You don't understand.
[snorts]
[Robbie clearing throat]
[Nate] No, no, I
don't understand.
But at least I'm trying.
You know all I wanted
was for you to ask me,
just once, how I'm doing.
You know, with work and
my little girl or...
I'm about to walk out
to 125,000 people!
You've got no fucking
idea what that feels like.
Yeah, and you've no idea
that I earn in a month
what you fucking
snort in a minute.
Or... or... or that
Kayleigh's shacked up
with some fucking butcher,
and so I'm living in an estate
surrounded by
fucking psychopaths!
Or that I only get to see my kid
for two hours every
fortnight or...
- So you need money?
- [Nate] Fucking hell!
You know, jealousy
don't suit you, Nate.
Jeal... Are you
fucking kidding?!
Alright, yeah, I might
have close to fuck-all,
but you, you have
fucking nothing!
[laughs] And this
coming from you -
a nothing, nobody cunt!
You know the difference
between me and you, Nate?
It's not my money,
it's not your kid.
It's the fact that I
had the fucking balls
to make something of myself.
[machine whirring continues]
[scoffing]
Yeah.
You bought a ticket
to the dream,
and the dream came true, and...
Yeah, fuck it, I am,
I'm jealous of that.
But you can keep
the fucking rest.
[machine whirring]
[air releasing]
[Robbie] Nate! Nate!
[engine revs]
[Robbie] Nate!
Fuck!
- Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
- [banging and screaming]
[birdsong]
[Peter singing] ♪
Somewhere beyond the sea
♪ Somewhere waiting for me
♪ My lover stands
on golden sands ♪
♪ And watches the
ships that go sailing ♪
And the crowd goes mild!
Time to get ready, youth.
Going by helicopter and all.
Youth?
Oh, Jesus Christ!
[sighing]
[Peter groaning]
Oh, shit.
Youth!
[exclaiming]
[Robbie chuckling]
[Peter] You bastard! I
thought you'd passed out.
I have waited my whole
life for you to step up.
[chuckling] And all it took
was booking the biggest concert
in British history.
What are you going on about?
When you left us...
Where's all this coming from?
All those years, I thought
he's just sorting himself out.
He'll miss me so much
and he'll come back.
Yeah, and I did.
Yeah.
'Cause Nan made you.
I didn't leave you with
nothing, though, did I?
Where do you think
your talent comes from?
Jesus Christ.
You've forgotten how
fucking lucky you are,
that's your problem.
It's a privilege
to do what we do.
What we do?
You live in a caravan.
You perform to fifteen
fucking people a night.
And I love every second of it.
And I don't need pills
to get me through.
[quietly] Fucking hell...
Sure, I'd give anything
to play to a big crowd.
Of course I would!
But if I only ever
played to one person
for the rest of my life,
I'd be happy giving them
everything I've got.
Unless that person
was me, though, right?
Really?! Who's been cheering
you on from the wings, hey?
Who was it who stopped ya
from ruining your career?
There wouldn't be
a Robbie Williams
if it wasn't for me.
You've always been there
for Robbie Williams, Dad.
Why couldn't you just
be there for Robert?
[Robbie] You off to watch
the football, then, yeah?
Nice one.
I'll see you in six years!
[shouting] You don't have it.
That's why you never made it!
[helicopter blades rotating]
Not as a husband, not as
a father, not as anything!
- [helicopter blades rotating]
- [wind blows]
Peter Conway doesn't
fucking have it!
[helicopter blades
loudly rotating]
[wind blowing]
[screaming loudly]
[breathing deeply]
[Robbie whispering] Everything
has come down to this.
They've come for me.
And I'm going to die out there.
This is the end.
[doors opening]
[grand music playing]
[epic orchestral music
rising] [crowd roaring]
[mechanism clinks]
Light 'em up.
[intro to "Let Me
Entertain You" playing]
[music plays over dialogue]
♪ Hell is gone and
heaven's here ♪
♪ There's nothing
left for you to fear ♪
♪ Shake your ass, come
over here, now scream ♪
[crowd screaming]
♪ I'm a burning effigy of
everything I used to be ♪
♪ You're my rock of
empathy, my dear ♪
♪ So, come on, let
me entertain you ♪
♪ Let me entertain you
♪ Life's too short
for you to die ♪
♪ So grab yourself an alibi
♪ Heaven knows your
mother lied, mon cher ♪
♪ Separate your
right from wrong ♪
♪ Come and sing a
different song ♪
♪ The kettle's on, so
don't be long, mon cher ♪
♪ So, come on
♪ Let me entertain you
Good evening, Knebworth.
[crowd roaring]
[camera clicking]
My name is Robbie Williams.
[woman screams]
This is my band.
And for the next two
hours, your arse is mine!
[cheering]
♪ Look me up in
the Yellow Pages ♪
♪ I will be your
rock of ages ♪
♪ See-through fads and
your crazy phases ♪
♪ Little Bo Peep
has lost his sheep ♪
♪ Popped a pill and
fell asleep... ♪
[Robbie's inner voice] We're
going to slaughter you.
You're fucking useless!
♪ Your mind gets burned with
the habits you've learned ♪
♪ But we're the generation
that's got to be heard ♪
♪ You're tired of
your teachers... ♪
[Robbie's inner voice]
You've got nowhere to go!
Do everyone a favour
and fucking end it!
- Bounce! Bounce! Bounce!
- ♪ Let me entertain you
[crowd roaring]
♪ Let me entertain you
[metal scraping]
[Robbie's inner voice]
There's only one way out!
You don't deserve
to fucking live.
You will never be enough!
[screaming]
♪ He may be good He
may be out of sight ♪
♪ But he can't be here
So come around tonight ♪
♪ Here is the place
where the feeling grows ♪
♪ You gotta get
high before you... ♪
[Robbie screaming loudly]
- ♪ Let me entertain you -
[thudding and metal clanging]
♪ Let me entertain you
[metallic clanking]
♪ Come on, come on
- ♪ Come on, come on - Whoa!
♪ Come on, come on,
come on, come on ♪
[monkeys roaring]
♪ Come on, come on,
come on, come on ♪
[child monkey] No, no, noooo!
Argh!
[groaning and moaning]
- [ragged final breaths]
- [music finishes]
[Robbie whimpering]
[whimpering]
[grunting]
[pants]
[distant singing] ♪ Come on,
come on, come on, come on ♪
♪ Come on, come on,
come on, come on ♪
[louder] ♪ Come on, come
on, come on, come on ♪
♪ Come on, come on,
come on, come on ♪
[both singing] ♪ Come on,
come on, come on, come on ♪
- Argh!
- [silence]
[grunting]
[blood splattering]
[heavy breathing]
[birds calling]
[Robbie singing in a whisper]
♪ Send someone to love me
♪ I need to rest in arms
♪ Keep me safe from harm
♪ In pouring rain
♪ As my soul
♪ Heals the shame
♪ I will grow
through this pain ♪
♪ Lord, I'm doing
all I can... ♪
[orchestral intro to
"Better Man" playing]
[sniffling]
[razor blade clinks]
♪ Send someone to love me
♪ I need to rest in arms
♪ Keep me safe from harm
♪ In pouring rain
♪ Give me endless summer
♪ Lord, I fear the cold
♪ Feel I'm getting old
♪ Before my time
♪ As my soul
♪ Heals the shame
♪ I will grow
through this pain ♪
♪ Lord, I'm doing
all I can... ♪
[woman] I lost the house.
The worst thing was I
lost the ability to care.
You are next, if
you want to share.
I feel a bit stupid,
to be honest.
I'm just a chav that got
everything they ever wanted.
It's a bit fucking
embarrassing, to be frank.
I was taught that fame
would solve everything.
But fame's got
fuck-all to do with me.
It's about acting out
everyone else's fantasies.
The shagging, the boozing, the
showing your bollocks on TV
and people cheering you for it.
Fame looks good in a photo.
They say your life freezes
at the age you become famous.
So I am fifteen.
I'm stunted.
I'm unevolved.
And that's why I'm always
like, "Oh, it's okay.
"I think I'm a cunt.
I'm fine with it."
So I get in there before you do.
And I fucking hate
myself for it.
Sometimes it's a curse to
get everything we want.
Repairing close relationships
is a good first step
to repairing ourselves.
[buzzing]
♪ Go easy on my conscience
♪ 'Cause it's not my fault
♪ I know I've been taught
♪ To take the blame
[orchestral choral music]
♪ As my soul heals the shame
♪ I will grow
through this pain ♪
♪ Lord, I'm doing
all I can... ♪
[bottle clinking]
[car approaching]
[engine starting]
[door creaks open]
[gentle orchestral music]
♪ Give me endless summer
Lord, I fear the cold ♪
[Nicole chattering]
You did it. And
you deserve this.
♪ I will grow
through this pain ♪
♪ Lord, I'm doing
all I can... ♪
[uplifting orchestral music]
♪ Lord, I'm doing all I can
♪ To be a better man
[TV playing]
[Robbie laughing]
[laughing]
[Robbie] Good evening, folks.
Good evening, you slags.
No, good evening, folks.
So, who is Robbie Williams?
Well, I've been
called many things -
narcissistic, punchable,
shit-eating twat.
But while I'm all those things,
I want to show you how
I really see myself.
So, sit back, relax,
while I give you a right
fucking entertaining.
So, the story starts...
[kisses]
[orchestral version
of "Feel" playing]
This is the last
song of the evening.
[audience aahing]
It's sadder than that.
[audience aahing louder]
It's much sadder than that.
[audience laughing]
Thank you for being a
wonderful audience tonight
and making my dream come true.
[applauding]
I want to thank my mum...
...for being there
when I needed ya.
[applause]
Always.
[mouths silently] I love you.
- [intro to "My Way" playing]
- [audience applauding]
You guessed it, folks!
♪ And now, the end is near
If you know the words, sing up.
If you don't, shut
up, it'll sound crap.
[audience laughing]
♪ ..the final curtain
♪ My friends, I'll
say it clear ♪
♪ And state my case
♪ On which I'm certain
[woman] I love you, Robbie!
♪ I've lived a
life that's full ♪
♪ I've travelled each
and every highway ♪
Come on.
♪ And more... Everybody!
[audience] ♪ Much
more than this
♪ I did it my way
Now, I couldn't finish the show
without mentioning
someone else here tonight.
I share a lot of the same
mannerisms as this person.
People say I sing
a bit like him too.
He's made me who I am -
all the good things
and a touch of the bad.
And I wouldn't be
where I am without him.
We haven't performed
together for...
...twenty five years.
But I've wanted to
every day since.
Please welcome to the stage...
...my dad.
[audience applauding]
[uplifting music]
[Peter] Thank you very much.
What do you think, youth,
shall we light 'em up?
Tell it like it is, Dad.
♪ Regrets, I've had a few
Me too.
♪ But then again
♪ Too few to mention
♪ I did what I had to do
♪ And saw it through
[applause and whistling]
♪ Without exemption
[both singing] ♪ I planned
each charted course ♪
♪ Each careful step
♪ Along the byway
- I'm sorry, Robert.
- I know, Dad.
- You always had it, you know.
- [audience continues singing]
Now, look at you.
You're one of the gods.
[audience] ♪ My way
♪ Yes, there were times ♪
♪ I'm sure you knew
♪ When I bit off more
than I could chew ♪
♪ And through it all
♪ When there was doubt
♪ I ate it up
and spit it out ♪
♪ I faced it all
♪ And I stood tall
♪ And did it my way
[audience cheering
and applauding]
[kisses]
[audience cheering louder]
Peter Conway, everybody.
My dad!
Or at least that's
what Mum told us.
[mouths silently] Oh, Robbie...
♪ I've loved I've
laughed and cried ♪
♪ I've had my fill
My share of losing ♪
♪ And now
♪ As tears subside
♪ I find it all so amusing
♪ To think I did all that
♪ And may I say
♪ Not in a shy way
♪ Oh, no Oh, no, not me ♪
♪ I did it my way
♪ For what is a man
♪ What has he got?
♪ If not himself,
then he has naught ♪
♪ To say the things
he truly feels ♪
♪ And not the words
♪ Of one who kneels
♪ Let the record show
♪ I took the blows
♪ And did it
♪ My
♪ Way
[grand orchestral climax]
[audience applauding]
[woman] We love you!
Nan! This is your grandson
singing and I love you.
♪ I did it
♪ My
♪ Way
[grand orchestral music]
[Robbie VO] Who did I
love when I was a kid?
I loved Frank Sinatra.
Come on!
And I loved my dad and
he's an entertainer.
Shit! That's who I am.
That feels good to me.
I want to make the
twelve-year-old at my nan's,
watching TV on a Saturday
night, feeling safe.
I wanted to make that
same twelve-year-old
feel safe onstage.
I'm a fucking entertainer.
It might be cabaret, but
it's world-class cabaret,
and I'm the fucking best at it.
Fuck yourselves!
[music crescendos and ends]
["Forbidden Road" by
Robbie Williams playing]
♪ I walked along
a forbidden road ♪
♪ I had to know
Where does it go? ♪
♪ Like birds that
fly into the sun ♪
♪ I had to run I'm
not the only one ♪
♪ Why do you look
at me that way? ♪
♪ I'm not a problem
that needs solving ♪
♪ The truth is still evolving
♪ Life is the choices
that we make ♪
♪ We're the masters
of our own fate ♪
♪ The painter and the paint
♪ You need to lose your mind
♪ To get back to the light
♪ Sometimes
♪ I walked along
a forbidden road ♪
♪ I had to know
Where does it go? ♪
♪ Like birds that
fly into the sun ♪
♪ I had to run I'm
not the only one ♪
♪ Maybe I'm never satisfied
♪ I made a lot of
poor decisions ♪
♪ Yeah, I made
some revisions ♪
♪ And I'm still trying
to get it right ♪
♪ I'm a living contradiction
The cure and the affliction ♪
♪ You need to lose your mind
♪ To get back to the light
♪ Sometimes
♪ I walked along
a forbidden road ♪
♪ I had to know
Where does it go? ♪
♪ Like birds that
fly into the sun ♪
♪ I had to run I'm
not the only one ♪
♪ So do you love me now?
♪ Or did I let you down?
♪ You said you wanted
all my secrets ♪
♪ So I showed you
all my demons ♪
♪ Do you love me now?
♪ I walked along
a forbidden road ♪
♪ I had to know
Where does it go? ♪
♪ Like birds that
fly into the sun ♪
♪ I had to run I'm
not the only one ♪